### BRENT JEREMY NELSON

BLOCKCHAIN | WEB DEVELOPER

brentjeremynel@gmail.com https://brent-jeremy.github.io/

#### **PROFILE**

A proficient blockchain developer with 5+ years of experience, interested in contributing expertise in web and blockchain development.

Capable of excelling as part of a team or individually in a fastpaced environment.

Deeply knowledgeable in distributed ledger, blockchain security, blockchain architecture patterns, and different blockchain standards and ecosystems.

I have experience developing DeFi, DEX, DApp, Trading Bot, Token, autonomous systems and artificial intelligence. I am fluent in Solidity, Web3.js, Python and JavaScript, and have worked on a variety of projects as a consultant, helping clients achieve their goals.

I have a lot experience efficiently coding websites and applications with modern Framework like Angular, React and Vue.

I am continuously trying to improve, learn more and gain new experiences.



#### SKILLS

React Solidity

Rust

Python

**DEVOPS** 

NodeJS

#### LANGUAGES

**English** 

SOCIAL LINKS





Thai









#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### PROLOCALIZE, CTO

AUG. 2019 - PRESENT Prolocalize - Thailand

Prolocalize is Thailand's most innovative and fastest growing company founded in 2017 with the aim of boosting the reach ofbusinesses andinformationaccessibilityacross theglobal community.

We are a team of young talented experts with passion and dedication for helping companies to promote their businesses and reach a worldwide audience via the provision of quality and speedy services with the aid of cutting-edge technologies.

We observe a high standard of professionalism by cultivating a strong work ethics geared towards continuous research and development.

Our work principle is quality focused and our management system supported by ERP is compliant with PMBOK, ISO 17001:2015, ISO 9001:2015 and GDPR 2016/679. In this company I have worked in ML such as ,NMT,AutoML,and so on.

I have developed our own translator and make one translator platform for company work with AWS Amplify + Angular.

And when I have some part time I developed some services for marketing youtube downloaders, transcribers, and so on.

The company's live site is https://prolocalize.com but it is on maintenance now.

We are training with big data now.

#### LUCKY SHIBA, CTO

AUG, 2021 - PRESENT

Lucky Shiba - United Kingdom

And from last year I have worked for Luckyshiba company. It is England company and the site is https://luckyshiba.org/lt is a Blockchain game company.

We are developing a shooting game and all are ready to the lunch game.

In this company, I was a solidity developer.

So I have worked from token deploy and game logic with solidity.

You can check our company members from https://docs.luckyshiba.org/team.

#### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

2019-2021

https://prolocalize.com

This site was developed in Wordpress by an old developer.

I have updated this site to react and added NMT

translators such as Google translator.

The backend was developed with python Django.

And the frontend was developed with react.

Now we are training more and more languages.

Also ,there is a task management system such as smart cat. It will be very popular in a few years.

#### BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER-DEX JAN, 2021-FEB, 2021

https://rskswap.com/

Uniswap dex site.

We deployed the router solidity contract to ETH network. And developed a site with react and interact to contract using web3js.

#### BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER-DEX JUL, 2021-AUG, 2021

https://admin.usth.finance/

Pancakeswap dex site.

I deployed PRX token on BSC network.

Deployed router solidity contract to BSC network.

So this is dex site for only PRX/BNB pair.

I developed a site with react and interact to contract using web3js.

#### BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER-STAKING MAR, 2021

https://bnbstaker.xyz/

This is BNB staking site

So If any user will deposit bnb then they will get a reward with bnb.

As you can see from the site there are 3 plans. 14days lock plan,21days lock plan,28 days lock plan.

#### EDUCATION

# Master's Degree King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

APR, 2013 — MAR, 2018

I graduated from King Mongkut's University of Technotlogy Thonbun.

King Mongkut's University of Technology
Thonburi or colloquially "Bangmod is an
engineering and technology university in Thailand
n this university I mastered in Computer sicence.
So my software development was started from
university.

In the university I learned web and Machin Learning.

So I worked easily in Porolocalize company after leave the university.

# Thai Solutions School in Bangkok

Apr, 2011— Mar, 2013

I have studied at Thai Solutions School in Bangkok for 2 years.

There are about 3 courses in the school and to graduate school, I should pass these courses.
I learned basic programming and mathematics in this school.

I love my school.

So users can withdraw the bnb that they deposited in 14days,21days and 28days.

The reward percentages are different too.

## NFT MINT MARKETPLACE SITES OCT,2021-NOV,2021

https://nft-mint.org/

http://www.soulhero.io/

The first site is only the NFT mint site.

It uploaded the image to IPFS and call a mint function

in the EERC712 contract that is deployed before.

And second is Solana Nft marketplace.

So on that site, you can mint NFT, list nft that you minted, buy and sell NFT, and auction method.

So users can bid the price for the NFT and the admin can accept the highest price

#### CASINO GAME PLATFORM

DEC,2021-APR,2022

https://game.babylonswap.finance/

The current game platform is working in BSC

But If anyone wants this game to work with their token I can try it in I hour.

For this game, we need 3 types of programs.

First, we need a game platform or we can say backend. And second, we need to build the current individual unity

And third ,we need to load the unity game and integrate it with our platform.

#### FORKING BLOCKCHAIN

DEC,2021-MAR,2022

Deamchain developement.

https://deamchain.com/

I have forkend FTM ,made exploer,dex,bridge,and farming and staking platform.

Deamchain is a fast ,high- throughput open-source smart contract platform for digital assets and dApps.